Vijay Kumar

Front-end Developer

_ _

Profile

Skills

Github: https://github.com/Vijaykumar308/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/viiav-kumar-679ab2221/

Portfolio: https://vijaykumar308.github.io/portfolio/

Mobile no. 8054975142 Email: jwvijaykumar@gmail.com

I have over 1+ year of experience in front-end development . I'm 23 years old and I live in Amritsar. Currently, I work as a Jr. Engineer in Kochar Tech.

HTML

•

Javascript

React is

CSS

Bootstrap 4

Git/Github

PHP

SQL

Experience

KocharTech/ Jr.Enginner

May 2022 - Present, Amritsar

- Developed a single handedly end to end application for the client in order to manage their data which includes **React js** as front end, **PHP** for backend and databases used as **MySQL**.
- Work upon a HRMS project where I got the responsibility to resolve existing bugs and write the reusable component and write down CSS to make it more user interactive.

Kochar Tech / Internship

Nov, 2021-April 2022, Amritsar

- Polished PHP and MySQL Skills
- Learned about CSS flexbox and grid write custom CSS to make application responsive
- Learn about git and github to work collaboratively with the team.

Education

G.N.D.U College Verka/ Bachelor of Computer Application

July 2018 - july, 2021, Amritsar

I did my Bachelor of Computer Application from Guru Nanak dev University College verka, Amritsar in the year of 2018-2021 passed with 67%.